Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- Audio
  - Ecklar, Julia
    - Julia Ecklar, Musecon 1; Julia Ecklar Recorded by Gary; Unknown - Source Tape #1 Part 1, Notes: Part of a pack - rubber banded together Origin:; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
    - Julia Ecklar Tape #1; Julia Ecklar Tape #2; Julia Ecklar Tape #3; Julia Ecklar Tape 4, Notes: Part of a pack - rubber banded together Origin:; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
    - Julia - Filk Sings and Bardic Circles II; Julia - Filk Sings and Bardic Circles III; Julia - From Leigh; Julia - Joeys recording; Julia - MuseCon 1989; Julia - Scratch #1; Julia - 1985, Notes: Part of a pack - rubber banded together Origin:; Burnt DVD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
    - Julia Eckar Palo Alto MP3 CD for Harold Stein, Notes: Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Ecklar, Julia; Burnt CD
    - Horsetamer, 2013; Notes: In a ziplock with bubblewrap. This CD is signed. Origin: Prometheus Music; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Ecklar, Julia; Prometheus Music; Professional CD
    - Freas Tape, Live @ Pam & Sandy's, Selected cuts from Traveller, Notes: Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
    - Walkabout, 1991; Notes: DR-10003 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_walkabout; Professional Cassette 5 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Ecklar, Julia; Professional Cassette
    - Julia Ecklar/Divine Intervention [WS], 1986; Notes: WS037 Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Julia Ecklar/Divine Intervention, 1986; Notes: AC-C103 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Horse-Tamer's Daughter, 1983; Notes: OCP-22: one copy missing liner notes Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Genesis, 1983; Notes: OCP-35 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_genesis; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Traveller, 1981; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - The Traveller, 1981; Notes: label on tape and case; no liner notes Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Ecklar, Julia; Tape
    - Space Heroes & Other Fools, 1983; Notes: OCP-16: line drawing cover; one on green paper, one on tan Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Space Heroes & Other Fools [gray background cover], 1983; Notes: OCP-16 Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Divine Intervention - Julia Ecklar 108, Notes: Realistic tape brand, with blue border Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Elgin, Suzette Haden
    - Suzette Haden Elgin / Song at the Ready, 1984; Notes: label only on one side of the tape; two different editions Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Elgin, Suzette Haden; Professional Cassette
    - Suzette Haden Elgin / Industrious Strength / SF Bedtime Songs and Stories, 1984; Notes: red case label; tape label doesn't mention "Industrious Strength" Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Suzette Haden Elgin 1984 / Songs from the Ozark Trilogy, Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Suzette Haden Elgin 1985 / Magic Granny's Songs and Stories for Children, Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Science Fiction Short Stories From the Ozarks, Notes: no case label Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Elgin, Suzette Haden and Farran, Randy
    - Soon to be a Major Embarrassment, 1987; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Elgin, Suzette Haden and Farran, Randy; Professional Cassette
    - Dragons, Cows & Kudzu [green cover], 1986; Notes: includes an illustration Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Dragons, Cows & Kudzu [tan cover], 1986; Notes: cover is just the Magic Granny Line logo Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
  - Ellis, Joe
    - The Dream Is Alive! Music of the Space Shuttles, 1992; Notes: TA 10002 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Ellis, Joe; Professional Cassette
    - The Synthetic Filker, 1991; Notes: TA 10001 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Ellison, Harlan
    - Remenisences of the Late Pulp Era, Notes: no case label Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Ellison, Harlan; Tape
  - Elman, Tony
    - Shaking' Down the Acorns Vol. 2, 1984; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Elman, Tony; Professional Cassette
  - Elms, Duane and Warner, Larry
    - St. Elmo's Fire, 1990; Notes: Origin: Firebird Arts & Music Inc FAM-10118: https://archive.org/details/filk_st_elmos_fire; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Elms, Duane and Warner, Larry; Firebird Arts & Music Inc FAM-10118; Professional Cassette
  - Emerald Rose
    - Emerald Rose, Notes: Origin: Random Factors Music, Torrance,CA; Commercial CD 1 copy; Random Factors Music (Box Box #03 (I))
      Emerald Rose; Random Factors Music; Emerald Rose; Random Factors Music, Torrance,CA; Commercial CD
    - Archives of Ages to Come, 2005; Notes: Signed by all the members of Emerald Rose Origin: Starbridge Studios July, 2005; Commercial CD 1 copy; Emerald Rose; Starbridge Studios July, 2005 (Box Box #03 (I))
      Emerald Rose; Starbridge Studios July, 2005; Emerald Rose; Starbridge Studios July, 2005; Commercial CD
    - Celtic Crescent, Notes: There are two copies of the liner notes in the case. Origin: Brian "Logan" Sullivan - Guitar, Vocals, Arthur Hinds - Guitar, Bodhran, Vocals, Clyde Gilbert - Bass, Percussion, Vocals, Larry Morris - Pennywhistle, Percussion, Vocals; Commercial CD 1 copy; Emerald Rose; Brian "Logan" Sullivan - Guitar, Vocals, Arthur Hinds - Guitar, Bodhran, Vocals, Clyde Gilbert - Bass, Percussion, Vocals, Larry Morris - Pennywhistle, Percussion, Vocals (Box Box #03 (I))
      Emerald Rose; Emerald Rose; Brian "Logan" Sullivan - Guitar, Vocals, Arthur Hinds - Guitar, Bodhran, Vocals, Clyde Gilbert - Bass, Percussion, Vocals, Larry Morris - Pennywhistle, Percussion, Vocals; Brian "Logan" Sullivan - Guitar, Vocals, Arthur Hinds - Guitar, Bodhran, Vocals, Clyde Gilbert - Bass, Percussion, Vocals, Larry Morris - Pennywhistle, Percussion, Vocals; Commercial CD
    - Four Fat Dads, 2016; Notes: Origin:; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #18 (X))
      Emerald Rose; Professional CD
    - Verdant, 2011; Notes: Origin: Starbridge Studios; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #18 (X))
      Emerald Rose; Starbridge Studios; Professional CD
  - Eng, Cecilia
    - Of Shoes & Ships, 2002; Notes: Origin: Firebird Arts & Music; Commercial CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Eng, Cecilia; Firebird Arts & Music; Commercial CD
    - Of Shoes and Ships, 1988; Notes: OCP-97 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Eng, Cecilia; Professional Cassette
    - Of Shoes and Ships 159, 1988; Notes: Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #30 (NN))
      Eng, Cecilia; Tape
    - 9 Cecilia Eng ... Live!, 1992; Notes: Firebird Performance Series Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
    - Cecilia Eng - Live, Notes: no case label Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Eridani
    - Another Dawn, 1992; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Eridani; Professional Cassette
  - Faber, Cat
    - I Promised Eli by Cat Faber, 2007; Notes: Audio CD Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Faber, Cat; Burnt CD
    - Dr. Faber's Medicine Show!, 2013; Notes: Origin:; CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Faber, Cat; CD
  - Faithful Sidekicks, The
    - *.* and other star things, 2016; Notes: CAF Records Origin: CAF Studios; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #18 (X))
      Faithful Sidekicks, The; CAF Studios; Professional CD
    - *.* and Other Star Things, 2016; Notes: Origin: The Pond Studio; CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Faithful Sidekicks, The; The Pond Studio; CD
    - Achievement Unlocked, 2018; Notes: Origin:; Commercial CD 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Faithful Sidekicks, The; Commercial CD
  - Farnworth, Jean & Evy Mayer
    - Double Trouble, Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Farnworth, Jean & Evy Mayer; Professional Cassette
  - Farran, Randy, Haden, Rebecca and Haden Elgin, Suzette
    - Christmas in Orbit, 1989; Notes: Origin: OCLS; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Farran, Randy, Haden, Rebecca and Haden Elgin, Suzette; OCLS; Professional Cassette
  - February Sky (Phil Cooper & Susan Urban)
    - Time-Honored Pathways, Notes: Hand written mini-post-it on the front says Harold Stein Origin: Susan Urban and Phil Cooper; Commercial CD 1 copy; February Sky|Phil Cooper|Susan Urban) (Box Box #05 (J))
      February Sky|Phil Cooper|Susan Urban); February Sky (Phil Cooper & Susan Urban); Susan Urban and Phil Cooper; Commercial CD
    - Goldenrod, Notes: Yes, we know that CDs don't have sides. But with the 21st Century attention span being somtimes a bit short, we have provided a possible place where the listener can take a break and listen to the second "side" later. Origin: FS 03 februarysky.com; Commercial CD 1 copy; February Sky (Phil Cooper & Susan Urban) (Box Box #05 (J))
      February Sky (Phil Cooper & Susan Urban); February Sky (Phil Cooper & Susan Urban); FS 03 februarysky.com; Commercial CD
  - Felsberger, Bernd
    - Brernd Felsberger - Live! Recorded live in Germany, Strange Phenomena Tour 2000, Notes: Possibly purchased via Michael Liebmann who is credited as making sales of Felsberger's CDs in America in the liner notes. Origin: -; Commercial CD 1 copy; Felsberger, Bernd (Box Box #03 (I))
      Felsberger, Bernd; Felsberger, Bernd; -; Commercial CD
    - Star Tracks 1995 - 1998, Notes: "This is a Special U.S. Edition Distributed by Michael Liebmann Only" Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Felsberger, Bernd; Tape
  - Felten, Will
    - Star Cool, Notes: Hand signed note inside CD case addressed to Eli (almost certainly Eli Goldberg) Origin: Ramwa Records; Commercial CD 1 copy; Felten, Will; Ramwa Records, P.O. Box 1388, Elkhart, IN 46515 (Box Box #03 (I))
      Felten, Will; Ramwa Records, P.O. Box 1388, Elkhart, IN 46515; Felten, Will; Ramwa Records; Commercial CD
  - Fish, Leslie
    - Skybound, 2006; Notes: Origin: @2006 Random Factors 3754 W. 170th Street, Torrance,CA 90504-1204; Commercial CD 1 copy; Fish, Leslie; @2006 Random Factors 3754 W. 170th Street, Torrance,CA 90504-1204 (Box Box #03 (I))
      Fish, Leslie; @2006 Random Factors 3754 W. 170th Street, Torrance,CA 90504-1204; Fish, Leslie; @2006 Random Factors 3754 W. 170th Street, Torrance,CA 90504-1204; Commercial CD
    - Avalon is Risen, 2012; Notes: Produced by Kristoph Klover Origin: Prometheus Music; Commercial CD 1 copy; Fish, Leslie; Prometheus Music (Box Box #05 (J))
      Fish, Leslie; Prometheus Music; Fish, Leslie; Prometheus Music; Commercial CD
    - Chickasaw Mountain, 1991; Notes: OCP-56: Hand-written J-Card Origin: Firebird Arts & Music, Inc., Portland OR; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Fish, Leslie; Firebird Arts & Music, Inc., Portland OR; Tape
    - Leslie's 12/12/99 Space CD eval, Notes: Return to Eli - Post-it says "Do Not Distribute" Origin:; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Fish, Leslie; Tape - Home recorded cassette
    - Carmen Miranda's Ghost, Notes: Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_carmen_mirandas_ghost; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Fish, Leslie; Burnt CD
    - Leslie Fish at Bayfilk III Concert & Hall Sing 95, Notes: label on tape and case Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #26 (JJ))
      Fish, Leslie; Tape
    - Magic, Moondust & Melancholy Songs By Mercedes Lackey, 1989; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Fish, Leslie; Professional Cassette
    - Cold Iron, 1986; Notes: OCP-14? Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Cold Iron [Schenck art credit], 1986; Notes: OCP-14?: includes Bradley W. Schenck credited with "Art" Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Cold Iron [no liner notes], 1986; Notes: OCP-14?: Just handwritten label on case; professional tape labels Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Cold Iron 66, 1986; Notes: OCP-14? Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Our Fathers of Old, 1993; Notes: RF-10001C Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Solar Sailors, 1977; Notes: FAM-10110 Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - The Undertaker's Horse [generic insert], 1985; Notes: OCP-48 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_undertakers_horse; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - The Undertaker's Horse [full-color], 1985; Notes: OCP-48 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_undertakers_horse; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Undertaker's Horse fish #8, 1985; Notes: OCP-48 Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Skybound, 1982; Notes: OCP-08 Origin:; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Chickasaw Mountain [OCP], 1986; Notes: OCP-56: one copy missing liner notes Origin:; Professional Cassette 4 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Chickasaw Mountain [FAM], 1986; Notes: generic insert liner notes Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Firestorm, 1989; Notes: FAM-10106 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_firestorm; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Firestorm [home copy], 1989; Notes: FAM-10106: photocopy of official liner notes Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_firestorm; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Folk Songs for Folk Who Ain't Even Been Yet, 1976; Notes: FAM 10109 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Leslie Fish Not Canned or Frozen, 1996; Notes: WS045 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Carmen Miranda's Ghost, 1989; Notes: FAM 10093 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_carmen_mirandas_ghost; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - Folk Songs for Folk Who Ain't Even Been Yet [home copy], 1976; Notes: label only on tape; case says: "Leslie Fish Records" Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
    - 2 Leslie Fish ... Live!, 1989; Notes: Firebird Performance Series Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Fish, Leslie & Alexander, Heather
    - Tapeworm I Parodies by Bob Kanefsky [barcode], 1989; Notes: FAM 10112 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_tapeworm_1; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Fish, Leslie & Alexander, Heather; Professional Cassette
    - Tapeworm I Parodies by Bob Kanefsky 172 [barcode], 1989; Notes: photocopy of the full official liner notes Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_tapeworm_1; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Fish, Leslie & Alexander, Heather; Tape
    - Tapeworm I Parodies by Bob Kanefsky [single-color cover], 1989; Notes: official liner notes, but handwritten label on tape Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_tapeworm_1; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
  - Fish, Leslie & Eng, Cecelia
    - Tapeworm III Parodies by Bob Kanefsky, 1989; Notes: Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_tapeworm_3; Professional Cassette 3 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Fish, Leslie & Eng, Cecelia; Professional Cassette
    - Tapeworm III Parodies by Bob Kanefsky 174, 1989; Notes: photocopy of the full official liner notes Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_tapeworm_3; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Fish, Leslie & Eng, Cecelia; Tape
  - Fish, Leslie & Hayes, Frank
    - Tapeworm II Parodies by Bob Kanefsky [barcode], 1989; Notes: FAM 10113 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_tapeworm_2; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Fish, Leslie & Hayes, Frank; Professional Cassette
    - Tapeworm II Parodies by Bob Kanefsky 173 [barcode], 1989; Notes: photocopy of the full official liner notes, using the single-color generic insert COVER, but the rest is from the barcoded version Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_tapeworm_2; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
      Fish, Leslie & Hayes, Frank; Tape
    - Tapeworm II Parodies by Bob Kanefsky [single-color cover], 1989; Notes: Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_tapeworm_2; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #28 (LL))
  - Flynt, Clif & Wessels, Mary Ellen
    - Fragile Wall, 1985; Notes: WS001 Origin: Wail Songs, Oakland, CA; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Flynt, Clif & Wessels, Mary Ellen; Wail Songs, Oakland, CA; Tape
  - Foye, Dene
    - For the Love of Haggis, 2014; Notes: Origin: Recorded, Engineered and Mastered by Rich Biotheton at Ace Recording, Austin, Texas; Commercial CD 1 copy; Foye, Dene; Recorded, Engineered and Mastered by Rich Biotheton at Ace Recording, Austin, Texas (Box Box #05 (J))
      Foye, Dene; Recorded, Engineered and Mastered by Rich Biotheton at Ace Recording, Austin, Texas; Foye, Dene; Recorded, Engineered and Mastered by Rich Biotheton at Ace Recording, Austin, Texas; Recorded, Engineered and Mastered by Rich Biotheton at Ace Recording, Austin, Texas; Commercial CD
  - Freeman, Nancy
    - Incompatible Software Blues, Notes: In bag saying "Please do not copy/share without artist permission!" Origin:; Tape 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Freeman, Nancy; Tape
    - Stardust County: A Melodrama in 3 Acts Act: 3, Notes: Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Freeman, Nancy; Burnt CD
    - Stardust County: A Melodrama in 3 Acts Acts 1 & 2, Notes: Includes a letter to Eli Goldberg saying that this is a recording of the live show at The Fiddler's Dream in Phoenix in the summer of 2001. Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
  - Freeman, Nancy Louise
    - Shouting Theater in a Crowded Fire, 1991; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Freeman, Nancy Louise; Professional Cassette
  - Fromm, Adam
    - The Elmsley Count, 2011; Notes: Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #18 (X))
      Fromm, Adam; Burnt CD
    - Opposable Thumbs, 2012; Notes: Origin: Sotto Voce, Gilsum, NH; CD 1 copy (Box Box #21 (D))
      Fromm, Adam; Sotto Voce, Gilsum, NH; CD
  - FuMP, The
    - Halloween with the FuMP, Notes: Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
      The FuMP; FuMP, The; The FuMP; Commercial CD
    - The FuMP Volume 29: September-October 2011, Notes: Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
    - The FuMP Volume 47: Sept-Oct 2014, Notes: Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
    - The FuMP Volume 42: Nov-Dec 2013, Notes: Put this CD in your computer to see Ookla the Mok's Tantric Yoda at Con on the Cob 2013 Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
    - The FuMP Volume 42: January-February 2014, Notes: Put this CD in your computer to see a video of the great Luke Ski performing "Fake Adult" at this 40th birthday party. Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
    - The FuMP Volume 41: Sept-Oct 2013, Notes: Put this CD in your computer to see a video interview with Dr. Pinkerton of the Consortium of Genius at ContraFlow at 2013! Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
    - The FuMP: Volume 44: March-April 2014, Notes: Put this CD in your computer to see the outtakes reel from Power Salad's "Corned Beef and Cabbage" video. Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
    - The FuMP: Volume 39 As Told By a Redneck, May-June 2013, Notes: Also contains a video of the great Luke Ski performing "Walking Silly" live at Full Monty Python. Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
    - The FuMP Volume 46: July-August 2014, Notes: Put this CD in your computer to see a video of the great Luke Ski performing "When You Wish Upon a Death Star" at Orlando Nerd Fest 2014! Origin: The FuMP; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP (Box Box #05 (J))
    - The FuMP 11 Sep-Oct 2008, Notes: Put this CD in your computer to see Robert Lund's video for I'm Everything and Tom Smith's entry video for the Evil League of Evil! Origin: FIDIM Interactive, LLC; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP; FIDIM Interactive, LLC (Box Box #06 (YY))
      The FuMP; FIDIM Interactive, LLC; FuMP, The; FIDIM Interactive, LLC; Commercial CD
    - Will FuMP for Food: Volume 12 Super-deluxe recession/depression Holiday Edition! Nov-Dec, 2008, Notes: Pop the CD into your computer to unwrap more presents from the FuMP to you! Origin: FIDIM Interactive, LLC; Commercial CD 1 copy; The FuMP; FIDIM Interactive, LLC (Box Box #06 (YY))
  - Gabriel Hounds, The
    - The Wild Hunt, 1997; Notes: CHGCS 1110 Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #23 (GG))
      Gabriel Hounds, The; Professional Cassette
  - Gallagher & Heart
    - Pre-Release Demo: FIRE DREAM Song for The Dreamsers, Total Confusion; Fire Dream, 1989; Notes: Origin: Firebird Arts & Music; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #20 (RR))
      Gallagher & Heart; Firebird Arts & Music; Tape - Home recorded cassette
  - Gallagher, Diana
    - Cosmic Concepts 2013, Notes: Audio CD Origin:; Burnt CD 1 copy (Box Box #04 (T))
      Gallagher, Diana; Burnt CD
    - 3 Diana Gallagher ... Live!, 1988; Notes: Firebird Performance Series Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_diana_gallagher_live; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Gallagher, Diana; Professional Cassette
    - Cosmic Concepts Complete, 1981; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
    - Cosmic Concepts More Complete, 1985; Notes: OCP-64 Origin:: https://archive.org/details/filk_cosmic_concepts_more_complete; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
    - Star Song, 1981; Notes: one copy published by OCP, other self-published Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
    - Cosmic Concepts [no case label], Notes: no case label; the two copies have DIFFERENT CONTENTS Origin:; Professional Cassette 2 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Gallagher, Diana G.
    - Cosmic Concepts, 2013; Notes: ocalamoon.com Origin:; Professional CD 1 copy (Box Box #18 (X))
      Gallagher, Diana G.; Professional CD
  - Gallamor the Bard (aka Steve Macdonald)
    - Drive By Barding, 2006; Notes: Recording by Steve Macdonald | Mixing and Mastering by Bill Roper Cover Art @2006 by Diana Harlan Stein (www.naiadstudios.com) @p 2006 thin Ice Records Origin:; Commercial CD 1 copy; Gallamor the Bard (aka Steve Macdonald); Recorded March 2006, Thin Ice Studios, Mixed April 2006 Dodeka Records (Box Box #03 (I))
      Gallamor the Bard (aka Steve Macdonald); Recorded March 2006, Thin Ice Studios, Mixed April 2006 Dodeka Records; Gallamor the Bard (aka Steve Macdonald); Recorded March 2006, Thin Ice Studios, Mixed April 2006 Dodeka Records; Commercial CD
    - Gather Day, 2004; Notes: Recording, Mixing and Mastering by Steve Macdonald Cover art @2004 by Diana Harlan Stein (www.naiadstudios.com) @p 2004 Thin Ice Records Origin:; Commercial CD 1 copy; Gallamor the Bard (aka Steve Macdonald); Recorded and mixed June, 2004, Thin Ice Studios (Box Box #03 (I))
      Gallamor the Bard (aka Steve Macdonald); Recorded and mixed June, 2004, Thin Ice Studios; Gallamor the Bard (aka Steve Macdonald); Recorded and mixed June, 2004, Thin Ice Studios; Commercial CD
  - Gambit
    - Voices From the Past, 1986; Notes: Blake's 7 and Sound of Music musical mashup (fannish musical?) This might be a copy of the original Origin:; Tape - Home recorded cassette 1 copy (Box Box #22 (E))
      Gambit; Tape - Home recorded cassette
  - Ganger, Victoria
    - NEANDIR Lady Of The Flame, Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
      Ganger, Victoria; Professional Cassette
    - Starmony, 1986; Notes: Origin:; Professional Cassette 1 copy (Box Box #27 (KK))
  - Gendron, Denise